hello everyone Merry Christmas and Happy
New Year to you I'm going to continue my
12 rules tour in January and February
will probably announce some more dates
in Europe as well for May and June but
we'll start with January and February on
Saturday January 19th I'm going to be in
Zurich Switzerland and then on Tuesday
January 22nd in San Jose California
Thursday January 24th in Riverdale
California and Friday January 25th in
San Diego California and I've got a week
or two off do some other things and then
I'm going to Australia and to New
Zealand on Friday February 8th and
Saturday February 9th I'll be in Perth
on Monday February 11th in Adelaide on
Wednesday February 13th in Melbourne on
the 15th that's a Friday I'll be in
Canberra and Saturday in Sydney on
Sunday February 17th I'll be in Brisbane
then I'm going to New Zealand Auckland
Monday February 18th Christchurch
Wednesday February 20th Wellington
Thursday February 21st Auckland Saturday
February 23rd then back to Australia
because we added some new venues to the
tour which was selling out quite rapidly
Tuesday February 26th Sydney Wednesday
February 27th Melbourne and Thursday
February 28th Brisbane so I'm looking
forward to seeing people in Switzerland
and in California and in Australia and
New Zealand and that should do quite
nicely for January in February and also
get my wife and I out of the cold
weather so that'll be good so I hope to
see you there thank you all for your
continued support in 2018 bye bye